<urlset
      xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1"
      xsi:schemaLocation="
            http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9
            http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9/sitemap.xsd">
<url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/testimonials/</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T16:32:18+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.8000</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/f7f8d5f2dfa9f190fd77e361e8eea991.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>George Gluski of AZ Talks About His Experience With Protect America Home Security</video:title>
         <video:description>George Gluski of Tucson, Arizona, provided us with honest testimonial wherein he speaks about home security and the installation of his daughter's GE wireless home security system from Protect America.  In home security and monitoring are important steps in making sure your family is protected and safe.

Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real alarm monitoring customers so that they could provide us with their honest feedback on our home security monitoring services.

Call today to learn how you can receive a free GE wireless home security system with purchase of alarm monitoring service. 877-814-8658

http://www.protectamerica.com/

And check out our channel (http://www.youtube.com/user/protectamerica) to watch our home security how to tutorials, other customer reviews, and our community involvement and fun videos.

Music from JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2012-04-04T04:28:49.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/PrEnRZlurxU</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>155</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/9c10d04b3a620e7822b4f978bb0985fc.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Real Protect America Customer Roy Thomas of  Winchester, VA Speaks About Home Security</video:title>
         <video:description>Roy Thomas, a real Protect America customer located in Winchester, Virginia, talks about the importance of in home security and expresses his pleasure with his wireless GE home alarm system and home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. 

Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real alarm monitoring customers so that they could provide us with their honest feedback on our home security monitoring services.

Call today to learn how you can receive a free GE wireless home security system with purchase of alarm monitoring service. 877-814-8658

http://www.protectamerica.com/

And check out our channel (http://www.youtube.com/user/protectamerica) to watch our home security "how to" tutorials, other customer reviews, and our community involvement and fun videos.

Music from JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2012-04-04T05:42:02.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/Fc4IWN33kk0</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>170</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/c772e583e6c0eecdcd79de7be0106b45.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Home Security Customer Review Provided by Randy of Leesburg, FL</video:title>
         <video:description>Randy, a real Protect America home security customer located in Leesburg, Florida, expresses his pleasure with his GE home alarm system and home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call today to learn how you can receive a free GE wireless home security system with purchase of alarm monitoring service. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:47:03.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/G7Jy-5pr49A</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>104</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/66b812a4da2a01dce46ac9230f4ef4fe.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Perry of Newton, MA Provides Honest Review of His Free GE Home Alarm</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear the testimonial of Mark, a real Protect America home security customer located in Newton, MA, as he provides us with an honest testimonial of his experience with his GE home alarm system and his home security monitoring provided by Protect America. 

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T21:05:05.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/xViE1vQbcbY</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>172</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/874862ca67264a400869c31bfee403a5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Alarm Monitoring Real Customer Review - Joe &amp; Nicki</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear real Protect America home security customer testimonial provided by Joe and Nicki of Livermore, CA as they express their satisfaction with their GE wireless home security system and alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call us today to learn how you can receive a free GE home security system with the purchase of alarm monitoring services by Protect America home security. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:40:55.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/op9Knxw1KjM</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>145</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/c08b02d1fd96bf0d1825a227c4ecd370.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Jose of Murphysboro, IL Provides an Honest Review of his GE Home Alarm</video:title>
         <video:description>Listen to Jose, a real Protect America home security customer located in Murphysboro, Il, as he details his experience with his GE wireless home security system and home alarm monitoring service by Protect America home security.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T19:59:05.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/63ksiZ9hqYc</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>97</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/4e8a90dca45ecfab4103c7e637040aba.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Simon Home Alarm System Review - Steve, New Market, AL</video:title>
         <video:description>Watch as Steve, a real Protect America home security customer located in New Market, Alabama, provides his honest testimonial of his GE wireless home security system and home alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Protect America sent Flip video cameras to real home security monitoring customers and requested honest testimonials of their experiences with their home security systems. Call today to receive a free GE home alarm system with the purchase of our alarm monitoring service. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T18:06:54.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/TS-FSXuv63Y</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>117</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/3e28231524404c50974091750db882c6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Rick and Sherry's Alarm Monitoring and Home Security System Review</video:title>
         <video:description>Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real home alarm monitoring customers and asked them to provide us with honest reviews of our home security monitoring service. Listen as Rick and Sherry of Bluefield, Virginia express their satisfaction with their GE home alarm system and alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call today to learn how affordable it is to protect your family and home with a GE wireless home security system. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:54:38.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/Td7CsZr3oys</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>175</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/617d98fb6f297f3d5172355828ac11a1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America - GE Home Security System Reviewed by Dave of Santa Rosa, CA</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear testimonial by a real Protect America home security customer, Dave of Santa Rosa, California, as he expresses his satisfaction with his GE wireless home security system and home alarm monitoring services provided by Protect America. Protect your home and family with a Protect America home security system today. Call 877-814-8658! 

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:07:46.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/LazmbcTcs7s</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>174</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/a562e59676e1b3c4e1068f5bc1b65bb5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Home Security System and Alarm Monitoring Review by Ralph</video:title>
         <video:description>Ralph, a real Protect America home security customer located in Fruita, Colorado, provided us with honest testimonial of his GE wireless home security system and his home alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real alarm monitoring customers so that they could provide us with their honest feedback on our home security monitoring services.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T21:21:28.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/XMC2E_QGCKs</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>149</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/bc7b14ef88e59eed48c79cd62d56ec18.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Wireless Home Security Review - Jane</video:title>
         <video:description>Listen to testimonial provided by a real Protect America home security customer located in Oly, DC, Jane, as she describes her positive experience with her wireless GE home security system and home alarm monitoring service by Protect America.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:25:42.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/h08RlK5TsbE</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>82</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/2c9aa46b15b0cd536b481a4ca03cf481.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Home Security System Review Provided by Mark of Ramsey, MN</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear the testimonial of a real Protect America home security customer, Mark of Ramsey, MN, as he expresses his satisfaction with his GE Simon home security system and alarm monitoring by Protect America. Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real home security monitoring customers and requested that they provide us with their honest reviews of our home security services.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T20:36:17.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/um3RtvbPRX8</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>173</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/82ef02a9964c5143c0ccff48388366b8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Simon Home Alarm System Reviewed by Delbert of Clinton, OH</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear testimonial provided by a real Protect America home security customer, Delbert of Clinton, Ohio, as he shares his experience with his GE home security system and home alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call Protect America today to learn how you can better protect your home and loved ones with a GE home security system. 877-814-8658


Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:13:36.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/s99bNITnGlQ</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>131</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/7088e87b1bfd6f4f42afb714658ea813.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America: Simon Home Security System Review Provided by Kerrie</video:title>
         <video:description>Listen as Kerrie of Colombus, Ohio describes her experience with her GE home security system and home security monitoring by Protect America. Protect America home security provided several of our customers with Flip-Cams so they could provide us with their honest opinions of our home security monitoring services.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T20:15:59.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/VgkcmISic4Y</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>160</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/8fdeeb015241888d0b2d5962f5672113.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Simon Home Security System Customer Review - Hugues</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear real Protect America home security customer testimonial provided by Hugues of Raleigh, NC as he expresses his pleasure with his free GE home alarm and his home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. Contact Protect America home security today to learn how you can protect your loved ones and belongings with a GE wireless home security system. Call today! 877-814-8658 

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:22:54.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/7PWOD1GX4cA</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>46</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/c56e0a7a8166e27f75fc7710839456ec.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Don's Review of His Protect America Residential Security System</video:title>
         <video:description>Listen to the testimonial of Don, a real Protect America home security customer located in Washington, Utah, and learn how a GE home security system and alarm monitoring by Protect America home security can protect your home and family today. 

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T19:19:45.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/YMuRG-VrF6U</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>120</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/c7d26842398f4991f6579b0470f30e22.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Home Security Monitoring Review by Jeffrey of Sparks, NV</video:title>
         <video:description>Jeffrey, a real Protect America home security customer located in Sparks. NV, expresses his pleasure with his GE home alarm system and home security monitoring by Protect America. Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real customers and requested they provided us with honest reviews of our home alarm monitoring service. Call us today to learn how you can better protect your home and loved ones with home alarm monitoring by Protect America. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:31:28.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/givPWanTvoo</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>127</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/ec458040d0f9a4fc9fb685d55f5ccba0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Gail of Rockmart, GA Reviews Her GE Wireless Home Security System</video:title>
         <video:description>Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real home security monitoring customers and asked them for honest reviews of our alarm monitoring service. Watch as Gail of Rockmart, Georgia expresses her satisfaction with her GE home security system and alarm monitoring provided by Protect America home security.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-02T19:39:55.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/cQf-bV09Jh4</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>123</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/2dd4e5477b0e7e31a0c7bfc18f3e268b.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Review of GE Home Security System Provided by Becky of Urbana, IL</video:title>
         <video:description>Protect America home security provided Becky, a real Protect America home security customer located in Urbana, Illinois, with a Flip video camera so that she could easily provide us with an honest review of her GE home security system and our home alarm monitoring service.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-03T17:04:08.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/NOiHDlNyhmI</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>120</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/8ab03831a3d28e7276414aa3a4c70e07.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Simon XT Home Alarm System Customer Review by Ingrid of Miramar, Florida</video:title>
         <video:description>Watch a testimonial by Ingrid, a real Protect America home security customer who resides in Miramar, Florida, as she details her experience with her GE home alarm system and alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Contact Protect America today to learn how you can receive a free wireless GE home security system with purchase of home security monitoring service.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-04T17:11:57.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/RYZjhKJ2i7w</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>187</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/240de1241fa18d75dcd354c264d10737.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Simon XT Alarm System Real Customer Review - Darrick</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear testimonial from Darrick of Ballwin, MO as he describes his positive experience with his GE home security system and home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. Protect America home security sent Flip video cameras to real customers and asked them for honest reviews of our alarm monitoring service.

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-04T17:08:37.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/IFL74_DpsLY</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>62</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/6c3b06aee90cd7a50ba45fb5423d8fe3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Burglar Alarm Real Customer Review - Nick, Brigantine, NJ</video:title>
         <video:description>Listen to authentic testimonial provided by Nick, a real Protect America home security customer, as he describes his pleasure with his GE home alarm system and home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call today to learn how easy and affordable it is to ensure the safety of your loved ones and valuables. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-04T17:25:51.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/6Pr4vlRLD9E</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>119</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/18c834d06dd61360c3e3e4bac0dfe329.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Home Alarm Monitoring Review - Roseanne</video:title>
         <video:description>Watch as Roseanne, a real Protect America home security customer located in Manhattan, Illinois, gives her testimonial describing her satisfaction with her GE home alarm system and home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call today to receive a free GE home security system with the purchase of our home alarm monitoring service. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-04T17:44:03.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/MQx7-BhkYcs</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>152</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/3da5cd8e33d9209fb90d5e181ce39e30.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Mike of Columbia, SC Provides Real Customer Review of his GE Home Alarm System</video:title>
         <video:description>Hear real Protect America home security testimonial provided by Mike of Columbia, South Carolina as he details his experience with his GE home security system and alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America. Contact us today to learn how you can get a free wireless GE home alarm system with the purchase of home security monitoring. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-04T18:06:28.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/JwXtsOCIN6M</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>285</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/8f4525a416550a8713faece7f089fd53.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>GE Wireless Home Security System Customer Review - Ralph, Fruita, CO</video:title>
         <video:description>Watch as Ralph, a real Protect America home security customer located in Fruita, Colorado, expresses his satisfaction with his GE home alarm system and home security monitoring service provided by Protect America. Call us today to learn how you can receive a free GE wireless home security system with the purchase of our home alarm monitoring service. 877-814-8658

Music by: JewelBeat.com
http://www.jewelbeat.com</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-04T21:51:54.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/BOS7r67CB48</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>116</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/news/</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.8000</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/8ca6a93a8256c51d3dc45f1f8b1116d9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Home Security Systems Protect America Home Security Systems</video:title>
         <video:description>http://www.ProtectAllTheThings.com with Protect America's "HOME SECURITY SYSTEMS." We provide the Best Home Security Systems solution available today. Whether you want protection for your home or even a small business, GE Home Security Systems from Protect America will fufill your home security system needs and most importantly, easily fit into your budget. The home security systems packages from Protect America combine the best price with the best equipment and service.

ZOMG! Are you a person who's looking for the best offer in home security systems? Then you've found the right video!

"O RLY?" you ask.

YA RLY!!! If you want to protect your whole home like a boss, then Protect America can help. We'll give you one of our free home security systems to keep your home and family secure. And we'll monitor it for a price that won't rustle your jimmies.

So if you don't want all your base are belong to burglars, call Protect America and PROTECT ALL THE THINGS!!!

Video by: Nicklaus Louis

Spokeswoman: Kristen Cottle

Talking Dog: Lucy

Talking Cat: Happy Cat

Leave My Walls Alone Guy: Nicklaus Louis

Angry Mobile App Man, Mover, &amp; Dancing Banana: Landon Kash

Scumbag Santa: Jason Garza

Pirate: Joe Delgadillo

Stealth Clown: Arick Casas

Overreacting Gorilla: Bradley Mann

Ninja: Syed Ahmed

Special Thanks to Rylan Francis, Jeff Butler, Matt Cardwell, Kris Clauson, Alejandra Ramos, Justin Gil, Nickko Nunez, &amp; Kelly Louis

If you're searching for information on the following: home security systems alarm system for the home home system alarm security system for home home security system home alarm security system then you've found the right video!

If you're like most families in America, your home is probably your largest investment, right? Why not take the extra precaution of providing the best in home security systems for you and your family? Protect America is committed to helping you meet your home security system needs and providing you with service you can depend on.

Visit http://www.ProtectAllTheThings.com to see why Protect America is the best option in home security systems.</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2012-05-07T20:01:13.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/r6Kk3QvW2_M</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>82</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/install/home-security-wireless</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T16:35:23+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.5120</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/41739356852d2c86ad4d9c6664454655.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Tutorial: Do-It-Yourself Installation of the Simon XT Wireless Home Security System</video:title>
         <video:description>http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/install

Installing and activating your Simon XT Wireless Home Security System is a very easy process that usually takes less than one hour. 

Make sure your home is protected and secure with a GE home security system and home alarm monitoring service provided by Protect America! Follow this simple "How To" video tutorial and get your home security system up and running today.

Our customer installation specialists are available by phone with step by step instructions. Simply call our toll free hotline, 1-800-951-5111.

Music by Gabriel Chance
http://soundcloud.com/gabrielchance</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-11-10T21:30:24.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/8t4pXGxBhqg</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>253</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/home-security-blog/uncategorized/5-necessary-home-security-devices-for-any-supervillains-lair_1595</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.4096</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/c531402f71c8a9358f0690f8bc16e42e.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Smoke Cloak Bank Raid (Abel Alarm)</video:title>
         <video:description>Smoke Cloak foils Bank Raid</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2007-08-07T10:51:41.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/ph_5fE20KJk</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>22</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/e7d2bbb25c250f5f1af3aab404c5de87.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title></video:title>
         <video:description></video:description>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/Zc_B5ertb1c</video:player_loc>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/f03fe9935c036f68418796d05a73b1e5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Parrot AR.Drone in action at E3</video:title>
         <video:description>Parrot's AR.Drone, a unique combination of fun, iPhone-controlled quadricopter hardware and a promising new platform for augmented reality gaming applications, will be launching in the U.S. this September at a price point of $299.</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2010-06-21T16:55:24.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/xQaiiofKwpQ</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>138</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/fd96f5dd4952ec9c961761efd324ed71.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Door Jamb Armor The Ultimate Door Security and Jamb Repair Product</video:title>
         <video:description>http://www.armorconcepts.com.  Door Jamb Armor® was developed by the partners of a real estate investment company with properties under renovation located in transitional areas.  Following several break-ins, increasing property loss costs, and several failed attempts to solve the problem with existing solutions, they began to consider new alternatives.

Our products strengthen the entry points on a structure and actually work to prevent intruders from entering an establishment, rather than simply alerting an owner that an intruder is already inside. The initial product is a fabricated steel solution that reinforces the existing doors on a structure and helps proactively prevent potential intruders from kicking them in.  The product is also a very effective and inexpensive way to repair previously damaged doorjambs.</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2007-05-07T19:41:08.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/0yjZRw5Ks3Y</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>77</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/329b2325d525672fe03ed627e86060ef.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>laser fence up and running</video:title>
         <video:description>blowing fog machine at the laser fence i built for phage/the institute</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-08-30T14:33:18.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/ax3gn71P8ys</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>121</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/home-security-blog/home-security/k-9-security-dogs_1671</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.4096</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/629c42d7b444d9ffb44c657946de52d0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title></video:title>
         <video:description></video:description>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/nirZWJ36GdM</video:player_loc>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/home-security-blog/home-security/protect-america-reviews-an-overview-2_1722</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.4096</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/6bad08f9124003db74cd6076b581255e.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Reviews</video:title>
         <video:description>http://www.besthomealarmsystemshq.com/Protect-America-Reviews</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2012-05-12T21:03:47.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/x4UWzsdI3sU</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>348</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/home-security-blog/home-security/protect-america-reviews_1025</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.4096</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/5b71016bd21ba18c82297cd4ffa4bc2d.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title></video:title>
         <video:description></video:description>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries</video:player_loc>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/home-security-blog/home-security/batteries-for-home-security-systems_1089</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.4096</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/346b8dbd69b298f3466047dbb437aa04.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Protect America Tutorial: Do-It-Yourself Maintenance of the GE Wireless Door and Window Sensors</video:title>
         <video:description>The GE Wireless Door and Window Sensors are easy to maintain. With proper care and service the sensors last longer and work better. Watch this tutorial to see how simple upkeep is on these devices.

http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/security_sensors/home-security-sensors

Video by Nicklaus Louis
Music by Gabriel Chance
http://soundcloud.com/gabrielchance</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2012-02-10T00:29:09.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/sIiPPE7H9j8</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>99</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
       <loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/home-security-blog/home-security/home-security-information/making-a-bb-gun-booby-trap-a-home-security-expert-analyzes-home-alone_108</loc>
       <lastmod>2012-06-20T17:15:19+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>0.4096</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/0bf8bf780fc7507ee96de68ef8ae224e.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>home alone traps. :)</video:title>
         <video:description>hope you enjoy this :))</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2011-05-25T13:43:48.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/W4An5VMZ9bY</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>136</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/6da8739ea587c7613cec767bb15cd02b.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Home Alone - Booby Trap Montage!</video:title>
         <video:description>http://www.youtube.com/billyandchucky
(Ask billy and chucky any question and have it answered!)

Montage of the hilarious traps Harry and Marv get into from the first movie!

What are the chances the exact middle of the video is that frame....</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2007-06-29T21:48:05.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/90FR8m-zEH4</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>87</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/750329391c922a45cf476244d650c393.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>YOUTUBE POOP SHORTIE: Harry Gets His Head On Fire!</video:title>
         <video:description>First YTP Shortiee with clips from Home Alone, Singin' in the Rain, TUGs, TTTE and the Mr Men Show (2008)

Enjoy! :)


Harry came to a house which havent been used, so he came inside to have a look, but Little Miss Daredevil had other ideas, When he came in, He got Fire on his head which makes him scream out loud all night long!


Will he ever get out of her devilish trick to survive?

Find out while watching the shortiee!



Dan5589

NOTE: All Things were Copyrighted to their Respected Owners</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2010-11-07T16:49:21.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/fcHk-aXjvWI</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>138</video:duration>
       </video:video>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>http://www.protectamerica.com/static/img/video-screenshots/5fe4b3ae44124b887f121cfb8bd97b5f.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Marv Scream!.wmv</video:title>
         <video:description>Home Alone scene.</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2010-11-22T19:58:14.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/embed/0Sz1j2Z7GQc</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>14</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>